[
{
    "id": "1",
    "question": "question1: 1+1",
    "choice1":"1",
    "choice2":"2",
    "choice3":"3",
    "choice4":"4",
    "ans":"2"
},
{
    "id": "2",
    "question": "question2: 1+2",
    "choice1":"1",
    "choice2":"2",
    "choice3":"3",
    "choice4":"4",
    "ans":"3"
},
{
    "id": "3",
    "question": "question3: 2+2",
    "choice1":"1",
    "choice2":"2",
    "choice3":"3",
    "choice4":"4",
    "ans":"4"
},
{
    "id": "4",
    "question": "question4: 4+1",
    "choice1":"14",
    "choice2":"15",
    "choice3":"4",
    "choice4":"5",
    "ans":"5"
},
{
    "id": "5",
    "question": "question5: 10+5",
    "choice1":"5",
    "choice2":"10",
    "choice3":"15",
    "choice4":"20",
    "ans":"15"
},
{
    "id": "6",
    "question": "question6: 66-60",
    "choice1":"6",
    "choice2":"7",
    "choice3":"8",
    "choice4":"9",
    "ans":"6"
},
{
    "id": "7",
    "question": "question7: 11*7",
    "choice1":"77",
    "choice2":"88",
    "choice3":"99",
    "choice4":"100",
    "ans":"77"
},
{
    "id": "8",
    "question": "question8: 88-80",
    "choice1":"8",
    "choice2":"88",
    "choice3":"888",
    "choice4":"8888",
    "ans":"8"
},
{
    "id": "9",
    "question": "question9: 915-15",
    "choice1":"900",
    "choice2":"90",
    "choice3":"9",
    "choice4":"0",
    "ans":"900"
},
{
    "id": "10",
    "question": "question10: 100/10",
    "choice1":"9",
    "choice2":"10",
    "choice3":"11",
    "choice4":"12",
    "ans":"10"
},
{
    "id": "11",
    "question": "question11: 7+4",
    "choice1":"9",
    "choice2":"10",
    "choice3":"11",
    "choice4":"12",
    "ans":"11"
},
{
    "id": "12",
    "question": "question12: 4*3",
    "choice1":"1",
    "choice2":"12",
    "choice3":"123",
    "choice4":"1234",
    "ans":"12"
},
{
    "id": "13",
    "question": "question13: 1333-1300-20",
    "choice1":"12",
    "choice2":"122",
    "choice3":"13",
    "choice4":"134",
    "ans":"13"
},
{
    "id": "14",
    "question": "question14: 1400/10",
    "choice1":"14",
    "choice2":"15",
    "choice3":"140",
    "choice4":"150",
    "ans":"140"
},
{
    "id": "15",
    "question": "question15: 500-485",
    "choice1":"15",
    "choice2":"25",
    "choice3":"35",
    "choice4":"45",
    "ans":"15"
},
{
    "id": "16",
    "question": "question16: 33+14-30-1",
    "choice1":"16",
    "choice2":"26",
    "choice3":"63",
    "choice4":"64",
    "ans":"16"
},
{
    "id": "17",
    "question": "question17: 37-10",
    "choice1":"27",
    "choice2":"17",
    "choice3":"7",
    "choice4":"2",
    "ans":"27"
},
{
    "id": "18",
    "question": "question18: 9999-1000",
    "choice1":"8000",
    "choice2":"8999",
    "choice3":"9999",
    "choice4":"10000",
    "ans":"8999"
},
{
    "id": "19",
    "question": "question19: 345+1",
    "choice1":"345",
    "choice2":"346",
    "choice3":"347",
    "choice4":"348",
    "ans":"346"
},
{
    "id": "20",
    "question": "question20: 44/4",
    "choice1":"11",
    "choice2":"12",
    "choice3":"13",
    "choice4":"14",
    "ans":"11"
},
{
    "id": "21",
    "question": "question21: 2500+25",
    "choice1":"21",
    "choice2":"2222",
    "choice3":"2500",
    "choice4":"2525",
    "ans":"2525"
},
{
    "id": "22",
    "question": "question22: 10*22",
    "choice1":"110",
    "choice2":"220",
    "choice3":"330",
    "choice4":"440",
    "ans":"220"
},
{
    "id": "23",
    "question": "question23: 23*0",
    "choice1":"23",
    "choice2":"230",
    "choice3":"0",
    "choice4":"1",
    "ans":"0"
}
,{
    "id": "24",
    "question": "question24: 24/2",
    "choice1":"11",
    "choice2":"12",
    "choice3":"22",
    "choice4":"24",
    "ans":"12"
},
{
    "id": "25",
    "question": "question25: 25/5",
    "choice1":"1",
    "choice2":"3",
    "choice3":"5",
    "choice4":"7",
    "ans":"5"
}
]